boostedboards.com 2017-05-19

# Privacy Policy | Boosted boards

Welcome to the website of Boosted, Inc. (“Company,” “we,” or “us”).  This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) explains how we collect, use, disclose, and protect information that applies to our website and our smartphone application (collectively, our website and our smartphone application are referred to herein as the “Service”), and your choices about the collection and use of your information.

Click on the links below to jump to each section:

  1. How We Collect and Use Information
  2. Sharing of Your Information
  3. How We Store and Protect Your Information
  4. Your Choices about Your Information
  5. “Do Not Track”
  6. Children’s Privacy
  7. Links to Other Websites and Services
  8. How to Contact Us
  9. Changes to Our Privacy Policy

* * *

### How we collect and use information

We collect the following types of information about you:

****Information you provide us directly:**** We ask for certain information such as your first and last name, phone number, address, and e-mail when you purchase products on our website, download or use our smartphone application, or if you correspond with us.

We use this information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Service, improve our products, as well as to communicate directly with you, such as to send you email messages. We may also send you emails, messages, or call you related to our products (e.g., order confirmations, technical and security notices).  For more information about your communication preferences, see “Your Choices Regarding Your Information” below.

**_**Use of cookies and other technology to collect information**_** ** **.****

We automatically collect certain types of usage information when you visit the Service.  When you visit the Service, we may send one or more cookies — a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters — to your computer or smartphone that uniquely identifies your browser and lets us help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the Service.  A cookie may also convey information to us about how you use the Service (e.g., the pages you view, the links you click, how frequently you access the Service, and other actions you take on the Service), and allow us to track your usage of the Service over time. We may collect log file information from your browser or mobile device each time you access the Service.  Log file information may include anonymous information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, information about your mobile device, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks and how you interact with links on the Service, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information. We may employ clear gifs (also known as web beacons) which are used to anonymously track the online usage patterns of users on the Service.  In addition, we may also use clear gifs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened and which links are clicked by recipients.  We may also collect analytics data, or use third-party analytics tools, to help us measure traffic and usage trends for the Service.  We may also collect data on your use of our products through our application, including board information and usage statistics.  These tools collect information sent by your browser or mobile device, including the pages you visit, your use of third party applications, and other information that assists us in improving the Service and our products.

When you access the Service by or through a mobile device, we may receive or collect and store a unique identification numbers associated with your device (“Device ID”), mobile carrier, device type and manufacturer, phone number, and, depending on your mobile device settings, your geographical location data, including GPS coordinates (e.g. latitude and/or longitude) or similar information regarding the location of your mobile device.

We use or may use the data collected through cookies, log file, device identifiers, location data and clear gifs information to:  (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the site; (b) provide and monitor the Service; (c) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, usage, and demographic patterns on the Service; (d) diagnose or fix technology problems; (e) updating our application on your mobile devices; and (f) otherwise to plan for and enhance the Service and products.

### Sharing your information

We may share your personal information in the instances described below. For further information on your choices regarding your information, see the section below called, “Your Choices Regarding Your Information.”

You agree that we may share your personal information with:

  * Other companies owned by or under common ownership as Company, which also includes our subsidiaries (i.e., any organization we own or control) or our ultimate holding company (i.e., any organization that owns or controls us) and any subsidiaries it owns. These companies will use your personal information in the same way as we can under this Privacy Policy;
  * Third party vendors, consultants and other service providers that perform services on our behalf, in order to carry out their work for us, or as approved by you which may include identifying and serving targeted advertisements, content or service fulfillment, financing, payment processing, or providing analytics services;
  * Other parties in connection with any company transaction, such as a merger, sale of company assets or shares, reorganization, financing, change of control or acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another company or third party or in the event of bankruptcy or related or similar proceedings; and
  * Third parties as required to (i) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, subpoena/court order, legal process or other government request, (ii) enforce our rights with respect to the sale of our products, including the investigation of potential violations thereof, (iii) investigate and defend ourselves against any third party claims or allegations, (iv) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Company, its users or the public as required or permitted by law, and (v) detect, prevent or otherwise address criminal (including fraud), security or technical issues.

### How we store and protect your information

****Storage and Processing**** :  Your information collected through the Service may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Company or its subsidiaries, affiliates or service providers maintain facilities. If you are located in the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that we may transfer information, including personal information, to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction, and you consent to the transfer of information to the U.S. or any other country in which Company or its parent, subsidiaries, affiliates or service providers maintain facilities and the use and disclosure of information about you as described in this Privacy Policy.

****Keeping your information safe**** :  Company cares about the security of your information, and uses commercially reasonable safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of all information collected through the Service.  To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity.  You are responsible for controlling access to your email communications from Company, at all times.  However, Company cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Company or guarantee that information provided by you the Service may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed.  Your privacy settings may also be affected by changes to the functionality of third party sites and services available through the Service.  Company is not responsible for the functionality or security measures of any third party.

****Compromise of information**** :  In the event that any information under our control is compromised as a result of a breach of security, Company will take reasonable steps to investigate the situation and where appropriate, notify those individuals whose information may have been compromised and take other steps, in accordance with any applicable laws and regulations.

### Your choices about your information

****Commercial and marketing communications:**** We use the information we collect or receive to communicate directly with you.  We may send you emails containing newsletters, promotions and special offers.  If you do not want to receive such email messages, you will be given the option to opt out or change your preferences.  We also use your information to send you email related to our products the Service (e.g., purchase and billing confirmations and reminders, changes/updates to features our products, technical and security notices.

****You control your account information and settings**** :  You can stop receiving promotional email communications from us by clicking on the “unsubscribe link” provided in such communications.  We make every effort to promptly process all unsubscribe requests.  You may not opt out of emails related to purchases of our products (e.g., purchase and billing confirmations and reminders, changes/updates to features of our products, technical and security notices).  If you have any questions about reviewing or modifying your account information, you can contact us directly at community@boostedboards.com.

****Online Advertising.   ****We may permit third party online advertising networks to collect information about your use of our website over time so that they may display ads that may be relevant to your interests on our website as well as on other websites or apps.  Typically, the information collected for this purpose is collected through cookies or similar tracking technology.  The only way to completely opt out of the collection of any information through cookies or other tracking technology is to actively manage the settings on your browser or mobile device.  Please refer to your mobile device or browser’s technical information for instructions on how to delete and disable cookies, and other tracking/recording tools.  (To learn more about cookies, clear gifs/web beacons and related technologies, you may wish to visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org and/or the Network Advertising Initiative’s online resources, located at http://www.networkadvertising.org). Depending on your type of device, it may not be possible to delete or disable tracking mechanisms on your mobile device. Note that disabling cookies and/or other tracking tools prevents Company or its business partners from tracking your browser’s activities in relation to our website, and for use in targeted advertising activities by third parties.  However, doing so may disable many of the features available through our website.  If you have any questions about opting out of the collection of cookies and other tracking/recording tools, you can contact us directly at community@boostedboards.com.

****How long we keep your information**** :  Company may retain your information that you have provided for a commercially reasonable time for backup, archival, or audit purposes.

### “Do not track”

Although we do our best to honor the privacy preferences of our customers, we are not able to respond to Do-Not-Track signals from your browser at this time.  As discussed above, we track website usage information through the use of cookies for analytic and internal purposes only.  Because we do not collect this information to track you across websites over time, your selection of the “Do Not Track” option provided by your browser will not have any effect on our collection of cookie information for analytics or internal purposes.

### Children’s privacy

Company does not knowingly collect or solicit any information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register as users of the Service.  The Service and its content are not directed at children under the age of 13. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible.  If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at community@boostedboards.com.

### Links to other websites and services

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites or services linked to or from the Service, including the information or content contained therein.  Please remember that when you use a link to go from our website to another website, our Privacy Policy does not apply to third-party websites or services.  Your browsing and interaction on any third-party website or service, including those that have a link or advertisement on the Service, are subject to that third party’s own rules and policies.  In addition, you agree that we are not responsible for and we do not have any control over any third-parties that you authorize to access your information. If you are using a third-party website or service (like Facebook) and you allow such a third-party access to your information you do so at your own risk.  This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources other than through the Service.

### How to contact us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the Service, please contact us at community@boostedboards.com.

### Changes to our privacy policy

Company may modify or update this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect the changes in our business and practices, and so you should review this page periodically.  When we change the policy in a material manner we will let you know and update the ‘last modified’ date at the bottom of this page.

_This Privacy Policy was last modified on May 19, 2016._
